In this course, you'll use the highly available constructs within
在此过程中 您将在以下时间内使用高可用性构造
AWS to create highly available and resilient systems and networks.
AWS 将创建高度可用且具有弹性的系统和网络
You'll build resources in the different regions and
您将在不同区域中构建资源
availability zones that make up the backbone of AWS Cloud.
提供 AWS Cloud 主干的可用性专区
Next, you'll design and build resilient and scalable solutions within AWS,
接下来 您将在 AWS 中设计并构建弹性和可扩展的解决方案
application services that allow for resiliency and geographic scalability.
应用程序服务 可实现弹性和地理可扩展性
Then, you'll explore connection between
然后你就会探索
all these technical aspects and business operations and objectives.
所有这些技术方面以及业务运营和目标
Understanding this relationship is key to delivering results for the whole organization.
理解这一关系是实现整个组织成果的关键
Finally, you'll practice what to do when things fail.
最后 当事情失败时 你会练习做什么
Things will fail, and here you'll gain knowledge and
事情会失败你会得到知识
skills to watch for and react to system failures.
对系统故障进行监视和反应的技能